https://www.freshbytesoftware.com/privacy-policy

Aaron from Red Tomato
Marcos from Transnational Food, Inc.
Dina from World’s Best Cheeses
Richard from Nicho Produce Company
George from VegiWorks, Inc.
CATCH FRESH AT THE SEAFOOD EXPO NORTH AMERICA BOOTH 471
JOIN FRESHBYTE SOFTWARE AT THE SUMMER FANCY FOOD SHOW AT BOOTH 647
Debuting the Freshest Bytes at Booth 3310
FreshByte is Ready to Heat up the New York Produce Show
Join FreshByte at Booth 471: See How Fast We Can Handle a Recall
FRESHBYTE SOFTWARE’S COO NOMINATED FOR HBJ’S 40 UNDER 40 AWARD
F/B Team
Trevor Morris (CEO)
Charles Butler (EVP)
Beth Jackson (EVP)
Lois Carlisle (DOO)
Support
Contact
Privacy Policy
FreshByte Software, LLC  operates https://freshbytesoftware.com/ . This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection and Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, email and phone number.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 % secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 21, 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgement of the modification and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
